JUJUTSU KAISEN
The Culling Game Part 1
Episode 57
Tokyo No. 1 Colony, Part 4
The rules' idea of continuation is
just a cover for the real plan.
Mark my words.
When only the strong remain,
Kenjaku is going to drop
a bomb on the game,
and the Culling Game
will fulfill its purpose.
I don't know what kind of bomb
Kenjaku's going to drop.
But it's going to happen
in the near future.
Maybe even this very moment.
That's why I'm preparing by
gathering strong allies
and stocking up points.
I have a few questions.
I doubt she's that strong.
That woman is bait to lure other Players
here for whatever reason works.
People tend to be less wary
of women, you know.
And when you're done using her,
you can just kill her
for her points, right?
What are you talking about?
I'd never do that.
Reggie-sama is my true knight!
So long as I serve him, he'll protect me!
How naïve and stupid.
Do you and your allies possess at
least 100 points between all of you?
Well, yeah.
A new rule will be added soon.
It'll let Players transfer
points between each other.
Hand over all of your points.
Negotiations have broken down.
He vanished?!
Hey!
Nue!
Whoa!
Hey!
Don't let me see your face again.
Oh. I get it, I get it.
I thought you were being lax,
but you can't kill us, can you?
You want the points we
possess, after all.
But...
if you don't fight to kill,
you'll regret it once you're dead.
Hey!
I'm down here, too!
Iori Hazenoki, Current Points: 35
He dead?
You're okay with this?!
This smell!
Is it over?
Reggie Star, Current Points: 41
Not yet.
He ran into a room before the
explosion, just like you.
Not bad.
But you wore him down a good deal, yeah?
Now you get it, right?
They have no intention of protecting you.
So if you understand that, then get lost.
Give it a rest already.
Then say it.
Reggie-sama said it for me!
He said he'd protect me!
He said he liked me!
So you say it!
Sometimes you run into them—
scumbags like you who are all talk
and no real action.
Thanks for that throw,
but now you're all battered.
Chizuru Hari, Current Points: 28
It wasn't easy climbing
all the way back up here.
Use the stairs, Neanderthal.
Ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong,
ding-dong, ding-dong!
A Player has added a new
rule to the Culling Game!
9: Players shall be able to view the
following information on other players:
name, points, number of
rules added, current Colony.
Rule 10: Players are able to
transfer a number of points
of their choosing to other Players.
Rule 10: Players are able to
transfer a number of points
of their choosing to other Players.
What kind of rule is that?
Max Elephant!
He did it again?!
You bastard! How dare you...
What am I doing?
I'll need more points in the future, too.
But Tsumiki won't be forced to
participate in the killing anymore.
Don't lose your patience.
Believe in the others.
Don't obsess over these guys' points.
All I need to do
is use my full might to brush
away any sparks that fall on me.
You have earned five points.
Man, what a waste of points.
How pathetic, getting killed before
he could even use his technique.
Did Remi drop out?
Even so, it's still two on one.
Damn it, I'm still feeling
that first explosion.
Fleeing is not an option!
Maybe I should use my domain?
But my domain is still incomplete,
so I can't close the barrier
and trap my foe inside.
The worst outcome would be them
running off and making me waste it.
Look out!
...out!
Two on one.
Do you really think that's a fair
arrangement?
Do you know what they
call people like you?
That's right! Cowards!
And cowardly attacks won't work on me!
Behold!
Zero damage!
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Fumihiko Takaba, Current Points: 0
Young boy! I'll help you.
I'm 35 this year,
so one look at someone's face and I can
tell if they're a good or bad per—
What?
You've got quite a bad look to you!
Whatever!
I use a relative grading scale!
Just like schools!
Schools use absolute grading scales.
He did protect me.
So I can trust him for now, right?
What do you make of that, Hazenoki?
I don't know him.
It's faster to just ask.
Hey!
Which type are you?
I get it!
You're asking me
if I'm funny
or not,
aren't you?
I'm not. I'm asking what era—
This costume I'm wearing
is modeled after the hero
who first made me laugh my guts out!
So to honor this costume,
I can't let my jokes fall flat!
Here's a gag I just thought of.
Try using it on your sweetheart.
Curse
Be ready for something!
"I don't want you as my Wi-Fi!"
What a shitty audience!
There are always jerks like you!
People who forgot how
to laugh in the womb,
and yet always sit at
the front of the venue!
You might be the problem.
Yet even so!
He has the same vibes.
I won't abandon you, either!
Because I'm
an entertainer!
He's fast!
His cursed energy skyrocketed!
The shift in output is massive!
This guy is strong!
Be careful.
I'm an old-school entertainer
who's pro-violence!
Now, what will you do,
young boy?!
We'll split those two up.
That other sorcerer is likely capable
of turning his body parts into bombs.
And he's using the reverse
cursed technique to—
You're too close!
Kogane!
Yes?
Pull up Hiromi Higuruma's information.
Itadori's the one who added that rule.
Search Results
Hiromi Higuruma
Points
Rule Added
Current Colony: Tokyo No. 1
Points
I'm done with this Colony.
If you'll back down, I'll let you go.
Huh?! Where do you think you stand?!
I need to recover the points
I lost from you killing Hari!
Hey, you.
It's Takaba!
If you're going to kill
that bomb bastard,
then if you can,
try to steal his points first.
Okay, young boy.
I accept your request.
But I'm an entertainer.
I'll never do anything that would rob
a person of their ability to smile.
As long as you win, I don't care.
Curse
Sparking!
What a dangerous technique!
Bam!
Time for fireworks!
However,
in variety shows...
He's gone?!
Red is banned.
Don't make light of m—
I'm glad you aren't my enemy, Takaba.
Now there's a line I've
always wanted to hear!
Later, young boy!
Don't die.
Aw.
That guy's dead now.
After that much mockery,
Hazenoki will get serious.
Worry about yourself.
I told you, didn't I?
I've already achieved my
objective in this Colony.
So now I can fight for real.
I won't hold back.
Max Elephant!
You even have one like that?!
You've figured out my
technique, haven't you?
But a water attack is pretty
simplistic, isn't it?
You manifest what's on those receipts,
but that's not exactly right, is it?
You're right.
It's hard to describe, but I'd
call it reenacting contracts.
For example, I can do this, too.
Contractual Re-Creation.
What I just used
was a receipt for a two-night, three-day
stay at the 5-star ryokan, Hoshizoratei,
complete with oil treatment.
In other words, my body is now
as refreshed as it would be
after resting up and relaxing
in a hot spring for two days.
Now, how are you faring in comparison?
You have injuries from our earlier fight,
and you've employed multiple
shikigami at once.
You must be exhausted.
I often employ multiple
shikigami at once.
The problem is that
one of those was Max Elephant,
which I usually use alone.
You can readily draw out and
dismiss your shikigami,
but that's not true once
they're injured, is it?
That's why you won't pull out your dog
that can run, attack, and defend.
Because of that,
you've been forced to use multiple
one-trick shikigami at once.
It's a battle of attrition where neither
of us can use big, high-output moves.
It's futile, see?
You can't kill me.
That's true.
In which case, I'll run.
Hold it.
It won't be that easy.
Mobile Terrace
Monday, November 12th
A community gymnasium?
Did he flee inside?
Or is he luring me in?
I could smoke him out with fire,
but getting into another
chase would be annoying.
Well, what shall I do?
Good. It's just as I imagined.
This is the perfect size.
What do you think you're
planning, you damn brat?
You already have something
set up, don't you?
All sorcerers tell lies.
The things I recreate are like shikigami,
so I can give them simple commands.
Knives normally don't fly, right?
Given your personality, I think it's
pointless to ask, but I will anyway.
If you give me your points,
I'll give you an easy death.
Barrier techniques are
difficult, aren't they?
No matter how long I've tried,
I haven't been able to get the hang
of placing an artificial space
of different size over reality.
Which is why...
No way...
I'm using this gymnasium as-is
to deploy my domain.
He can use that?
Domain Expansion:
Chimera Shadow Garden.
Domain Expansion: Chimera Shadow Garden
He's a sorcerer on that level?!
I never said I didn't have big moves.
Even if it's incomplete,
a domain is still a domain!
I'm pulling out my trump
card and activating it!
Not yet! Endure a little longer!
I acknowledge your strength.
Which of us will get crushed first?!
Get crushed!
Next Episode
Tokyo No. 1 Colony, Part 5